<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Mix Master</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Vodka</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Rum</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Gin</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Whiskey</string>
    <string name="title_section5">Tequila</string>
    <string name="title_section6">Extras</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="screwdriver_desc">A screwdriver is a popular alcoholic highball drink made with orange juice and vodka.</string>
    <string name="screwdriver_recipe">Mix equal parts Vodka, orange soda, and orange juice. Can also be made with other fruit juices.</string>

    <string name="jagerbomb_desc">The Jägerbomb is a bomb shot mixed drink that involves a shot of Jägermeister and a glass of beer.</string>
    <string name="jagerbomb_recipe">Fill a standard bar glass about one-third to one-half with beer or Red Bull and then drop a shot of Jager in.</string>

    <string name="gin_tonic_desc">A gin and tonic is a highball cocktail made with gin and tonic water poured over ice.</string>
    <string name="gin_tonic_recipe">Mix two parts Gin and three parts tonic water. Garnish with lime and/or lemon to taste.</string>

    <string name="fuzzynavel_desc">A fuzzy navel is a mixed drink made from peach schnapps and orange juice.</string>
    <string name="fuzzynavel_recipe">Mix equal parts peach schnapps and orange juice. Garnish with slice of orange</string>

    <string name="cactuscooler_desc">Cactus Cooler is an orange-pineapple soft drink</string>
    <string name="cactuscooler_recipe">Fill a shot glass half with triple sec, half mandarin vodka, then drop into a pint glass half-filled with Rockstar energy drink, and serve.</string>

    <string name="irishcarbomb_desc">An Irish Car Bomb is an American beer cocktail that is drunk as a bomb shot.</string>
    <string name="irishccarbomb_recipe">Fill a standard bar glass about one-third to one-half with Guinness and then mix equal parts Baileys and Jameson in a shot glass. Drop the shot in and drink while fizzing.</string>

    <string name="rum_coke_desc">A highball made of cola, lime, and dark or light rum.</string>
    <string name="rum_coke_recipe">Mix 1 part rum and 4 parts Coke. Mix and garnish with a slice of lime.</string>

    <string name="pina_desc">Do you like Pina Coladas? And getting ccaught in the rain?</string>
    <string name="pina_recipe">Blend together 1.5 ounces coconut cream, 1.5 ounces pineapple juice, 1 ounce rum, 1 ounce coconut rum and garnish with pineapple wedge.</string>

    <string name="daiquiri_desc">Named after a Cuban iron mine, this drink is a old favorite.</string>
    <string name="daiquiri_recipe">Shake 1.5 ounces of light rum, .75 ounce of lime juice, and .25 ounce simple syrup together, then pour and enjoy</string>

    <string name="martini_desc">The names Bond, James Bond.</string>
    <string name="martini_recipe">Shake or stir 2.5 ounces Gin and .5 ounce dry vermouth then strain into a chilled cocktail glass. Garnish with lemon twist or olive.</string>

    <string name="tom_collins_desc">Tom Collins???</string>
    <string name="tom_collins_recipe">In a cocktail shaker mix 2 ounces gin, 1 ounce lemon juice and 1 tsp sugar. Shake and pour into cocktail glass, add 3 ounces club soda and garnish with cherry.</string>

    <string name="margarita_desc">The margarita is a cocktail consisting of tequila, triple sec and lime or lemon juice, often served with salt on the rim of the glass.</string>
    <string name="margarita_recipe">Mix 7 parts Tequila, 4 parts Triple Sec (orange Liquer), and 3 parts Lime juice.</string>




    <string-array name="pantry_options">
        <item>Reb Bull</item>
        <item>Triple Sec</item>
        <item>Bailey\'s</item>
        <item>Jameson</item>
        <item>Vermouth</item>
        <item>Peach Schnapps</item>
        <item>Gin</item>
        <item>Vodka</item>
        <item>Rum</item>
        <item>Whiskey</item>
        <item>Tequila</item>
        <item>Jagermeister</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
